孩子：This place...
这个地方
孩子：Where is it?
这是哪里啊
妈妈：At the border of the spirit world.
在灵界的边缘
妈妈：I must be crossing over it very soon.
我不久就必须要跨过去了
孩子：Crossing over?
跨过去
孩子：Oh, yeah, right.
哦 对啊 没错
孩子：It happened so long ago I keep forgetting you're dead.
这发生在太久之前了 我一直忘记你已经去世了
Inuyasha, you, you've become a man, haven't you?
妈妈：犬夜叉 你是男人了 对吗
Well, yeah, I mean when you died
孩子：嗯 是的 我是说 你死的时候
I was still just a kid, right?
孩子：我仍然只是个孩子 是吗
Such terrible violent days!
妈妈：那些可怕的充满暴力的日子
And you all alone when no one to care for you?
妈妈：而那个时候你独自一人 没有人关心你
How can you ever forgive me?
妈妈：你怎么能原谅我呢
It weren't that a big deal!
孩子：那没什么大不了的
I mean...
孩子：我是说
Inuyasha...
妈妈：夜叉